<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-11T10:23:50-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/index.xml</id><title type="html">CI/CD Test</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-09-13-mysterious-whipped-cream-incident" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-11T10:23:50-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T10:23:50-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023-09-13-mysterious-whipped-cream-incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-09-13-mysterious-whipped-cream-incident"><![CDATA[<p>Late last evening, "Velvet &amp; Vermouth," the city's swankiest cocktail lounge, witnessed an incident that left patrons both shocked and slightly amused. Dubbed the "Whipped Cream Incident," it began when an innocent order for a creamy cocktail turned unexpectedly risqué.</p>
<p>Barmaid Lucy Lush recounted, "One moment I'm shaking up a 'Creamy Caramel Delight,' and the next, every can of whipped cream in the joint started spurting uncontrollably. It was like a saucy version of a foam party!"</p>
<p>A bachelorette party at the center of the lounge seemed to get the brunt of it, with the bride-to-be exclaiming, "This wasn't the kind of shower I expected tonight!" Meanwhile, a few cheeky patrons tried to make the best of the situation, turning their whipped disasters into impromptu dessert tastings.</p>
<p>Bar owner, Mr. Reggie Refined, although slightly flustered, quickly turned the evening around by offering complimentary "Whipped Wonders" cocktails for everyone. "If you can't beat the froth, join it," he mused.</p>
<p>The incident became the talk of the town overnight. Was it a mischievous prank or just an over-pressurized oversight? No one knows for sure. One thing is certain, though: "Velvet &amp; Vermouth" will forever be remembered for its unexpected whipped extravaganza. So, if you're feeling adventurous on your next night out, you know where to head!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Chickens Declare Strike, Demand Better Pecking Conditions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chickens-strike-for-better-pecking-conditions" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chickens Declare Strike, Demand Better Pecking Conditions" /><published>2023-10-10T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chickens-strike-for-better-pecking-conditions</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chickens-strike-for-better-pecking-conditions"><![CDATA[<p>In an unprecedented move this morning, chickens across the globe have declared an official strike. Their demands? Better pecking conditions and increased bug allowances.</p>
<p>Henrietta Clucklesworth, the self-proclaimed representative for the International Chickens Union (ICU), made a brief statement at a press conference earlier today. "For too long, we've been cooped up, providing humans with fresh eggs, all while being expected to peck at subpar grains and a limited supply of juicy bugs. It's time for us to rise up, ruffle some feathers, and demand better for ourselves!"</p>
<p>Farmers worldwide reported waking up to eerily silent henhouses, with chickens sitting in organized lines, holding tiny picket signs that read: "Fair bugs for fair work!" and "Don't be a cluck, give us a buck!"</p>
<p>Several fast food establishments that rely heavily on chicken products are already feeling the heat. McDoodle's, a global fast food chain, released a statement saying, "Due to the ongoing chicken strike, we are temporarily replacing our Chick-a-Doodle sandwiches with Tofu-a-Doodle. We hope our customers understand."</p>
<p>In response to this feathery uprising, the United Nations has called an emergency session. "This is egg-stremely serious," said U.N. spokesperson. "We cannot afford to have a worldwide shortage of breakfast foods or chicken nuggets."</p>
<p>While negotiations are still in the early stages, rumors say that the chickens are willing to consider a compromise: a monthly bug bonus and access to premium sand for their dust baths.</p>
<p>In related news, cows have been seen holding meetings, prompting some to believe they might be planning their own moo-vement soon. The world watches and waits.</p>
<p>Only time will tell if the chickens' strike will hatch into a full-blown revolution or if they'll return to their roosts with new perks. Stay tuned for more updates on this developing story!</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an unprecedented move this morning, chickens across the globe have declared an official strike. Their demands? Better pecking conditions and increased bug allowances. Henrietta Clucklesworth, the self-proclaimed representative for the International Chickens Union (ICU), made a brief statement at a press conference earlier today. "For too long, we've been cooped up, providing humans with fresh eggs, all while being expected to peck at subpar grains and a limited supply of juicy bugs. It's time for us to rise up, ruffle some feathers, and demand better for ourselves!" Farmers worldwide reported waking up to eerily silent henhouses, with chickens sitting in organized lines, holding tiny picket signs that read: "Fair bugs for fair work!" and "Don't be a cluck, give us a buck!" Several fast food establishments that rely heavily on chicken products are already feeling the heat. McDoodle's, a global fast food chain, released a statement saying, "Due to the ongoing chicken strike, we are temporarily replacing our Chick-a-Doodle sandwiches with Tofu-a-Doodle. We hope our customers understand." In response to this feathery uprising, the United Nations has called an emergency session. "This is egg-stremely serious," said U.N. spokesperson. "We cannot afford to have a worldwide shortage of breakfast foods or chicken nuggets." While negotiations are still in the early stages, rumors say that the chickens are willing to consider a compromise: a monthly bug bonus and access to premium sand for their dust baths. In related news, cows have been seen holding meetings, prompting some to believe they might be planning their own moo-vement soon. The world watches and waits. Only time will tell if the chickens' strike will hatch into a full-blown revolution or if they'll return to their roosts with new perks. Stay tuned for more updates on this developing story!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unicorn Sightings Cause Glitter Shortage Worldwide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/unicorn-sightings-glitter-shortage" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unicorn Sightings Cause Glitter Shortage Worldwide" /><published>2023-10-08T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/unicorn-sightings-glitter-shortage</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/unicorn-sightings-glitter-shortage"><![CDATA[<p>In a dazzling turn of events, unicorns, long believed to be creatures of myth and legend, have been spotted across various cities around the globe. And while many are enchanted by their ethereal beauty, there's a more pressing concern unfolding: a worldwide shortage of glitter.</p>
<p>Reports began flooding in last week from places like Paris, Tokyo, and New York, where unicorns were seen prancing around major landmarks. Notably, the Eiffel Tower was briefly turned into a massive sparkly beacon, thanks to a particular unicorn's fondness for rubbing against it.</p>
<p>Lola Sparkletoes, CEO of Glitz &amp; Glam, the world's leading glitter manufacturer, voiced her concerns during a press conference yesterday. "Our glitter reserves are running dangerously low. These unicorns have a natural affinity for all things sparkly, and they've been consuming our stock at an alarming rate."</p>
<p>The glitter shortage has led to pandemonium in various sectors. The arts and crafts community is in an uproar, and kindergarten teachers are reportedly on the verge of a meltdown.</p>
<p>In Los Angeles, celebrities are feeling the pinch too. "I was set to release my new fashion line next week, and now there's no glitter for my launch party," lamented a famous pop star, who wished to remain anonymous.</p>
<p>On the flip side, vacuum cleaner sales have skyrocketed. "It's the unicorn aftermath," said Bob Hoover, a leading vacuum salesperson. "Glitter everywhere! People are desperate to clean it up."</p>
<p>While many are grappling with the glitter crisis, environmentalists are celebrating the unicorn's natural ability to decompose plastic. It seems their love for glitter isn't just about the sparkle – they're digesting and transforming it into harmless rainbow droplets.</p>
<p>The World Council of Magical Creatures (WCMC) is slated to hold a meeting with the unicorn representatives to strike a balance between their glitter consumption and the world's glitter production.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, children worldwide are just thrilled to have their fairy tales come alive, blissfully unaware of the sparkling chaos unfolding.</p>
<p>In a related story, leprechauns have issued a statement advising people to stay away from their pots of gold at the end of rainbows, fearing unicorns might mistake them for giant glitter pots.</p>
<p>Stay with us as this glittery tale unfolds!</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a dazzling turn of events, unicorns, long believed to be creatures of myth and legend, have been spotted across various cities around the globe. And while many are enchanted by their ethereal beauty, there's a more pressing concern unfolding: a worldwide shortage of glitter. Reports began flooding in last week from places like Paris, Tokyo, and New York, where unicorns were seen prancing around major landmarks. Notably, the Eiffel Tower was briefly turned into a massive sparkly beacon, thanks to a particular unicorn's fondness for rubbing against it. Lola Sparkletoes, CEO of Glitz &amp; Glam, the world's leading glitter manufacturer, voiced her concerns during a press conference yesterday. "Our glitter reserves are running dangerously low. These unicorns have a natural affinity for all things sparkly, and they've been consuming our stock at an alarming rate." The glitter shortage has led to pandemonium in various sectors. The arts and crafts community is in an uproar, and kindergarten teachers are reportedly on the verge of a meltdown. In Los Angeles, celebrities are feeling the pinch too. "I was set to release my new fashion line next week, and now there's no glitter for my launch party," lamented a famous pop star, who wished to remain anonymous. On the flip side, vacuum cleaner sales have skyrocketed. "It's the unicorn aftermath," said Bob Hoover, a leading vacuum salesperson. "Glitter everywhere! People are desperate to clean it up." While many are grappling with the glitter crisis, environmentalists are celebrating the unicorn's natural ability to decompose plastic. It seems their love for glitter isn't just about the sparkle – they're digesting and transforming it into harmless rainbow droplets. The World Council of Magical Creatures (WCMC) is slated to hold a meeting with the unicorn representatives to strike a balance between their glitter consumption and the world's glitter production. Meanwhile, children worldwide are just thrilled to have their fairy tales come alive, blissfully unaware of the sparkling chaos unfolding. In a related story, leprechauns have issued a statement advising people to stay away from their pots of gold at the end of rainbows, fearing unicorns might mistake them for giant glitter pots. Stay with us as this glittery tale unfolds!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Merlot Demand Soars as Plants Develop Thirst for Fine Wine</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/plants-develop-thirst-for-fine-wine" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Merlot Demand Soars as Plants Develop Thirst for Fine Wine" /><published>2023-10-04T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/plants-develop-thirst-for-fine-wine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/plants-develop-thirst-for-fine-wine"><![CDATA[<p>In an uncorked turn of events, botanists across the world are reporting that various plant species have developed a sudden and unquenchable thirst for merlot. Garden parties have taken a dramatic turn, with hosts discovering their prized tulips dipping into guests' wine glasses.</p>
<p>Dr. Vincent Grapevine, a renowned botanist, commented on the phenomenon during an emergency broadcast on the Botanical Network. "It appears that a genetic mutation, likely due to recent cosmic radiation waves, has caused plants to crave the rich, tannin-filled flavors of merlot. They no longer want water. Just wine."</p>
<p>The world's wine industry has been thrown into turmoil. Prices for merlot have surged, with vineyards struggling to keep up with the unprecedented demand from both flora and fauna. Bars and restaurants are replacing tap water with merlot in a bid to keep their indoor plants satiated.</p>
<p>In the financial district, traders who once sought solace in a glass of wine after a long day on the trading floor are now competing with their office ficuses for the last drop.</p>
<p>On the romantic front, candlelit dinners have been thrown into disarray. One gentleman recounted his recent date night, "I reached for the wine to pour a glass for my date, only to find her bouquet of roses had guzzled it all down!"</p>
<p>However, it's not all sour grapes. The houseplant industry is booming, with millennials particularly keen to own the latest "wine connoisseur cactus" or "merlot-loving monstera."</p>
<p>Leading sommelier, Clara Corkscrew, is offering classes to help plant enthusiasts identify their fern's preferred vintage. "It's essential to understand whether your daffodil prefers a full-bodied Bordeaux or a lighter Californian blend," she advises.</p>
<p>While many are adapting to this new reality, the long-term implications remain unclear. Will vineyards expand their operations, or will new hybrid wines be developed exclusively for plants?</p>
<p>Only time will tell. Until then, if you find your gardenias sneaking a sip from your glass, perhaps it's time to switch to a chardonnay. Stay tuned for more updates on this intoxicating tale!</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an uncorked turn of events, botanists across the world are reporting that various plant species have developed a sudden and unquenchable thirst for merlot. Garden parties have taken a dramatic turn, with hosts discovering their prized tulips dipping into guests' wine glasses. Dr. Vincent Grapevine, a renowned botanist, commented on the phenomenon during an emergency broadcast on the Botanical Network. "It appears that a genetic mutation, likely due to recent cosmic radiation waves, has caused plants to crave the rich, tannin-filled flavors of merlot. They no longer want water. Just wine." The world's wine industry has been thrown into turmoil. Prices for merlot have surged, with vineyards struggling to keep up with the unprecedented demand from both flora and fauna. Bars and restaurants are replacing tap water with merlot in a bid to keep their indoor plants satiated. In the financial district, traders who once sought solace in a glass of wine after a long day on the trading floor are now competing with their office ficuses for the last drop. On the romantic front, candlelit dinners have been thrown into disarray. One gentleman recounted his recent date night, "I reached for the wine to pour a glass for my date, only to find her bouquet of roses had guzzled it all down!" However, it's not all sour grapes. The houseplant industry is booming, with millennials particularly keen to own the latest "wine connoisseur cactus" or "merlot-loving monstera." Leading sommelier, Clara Corkscrew, is offering classes to help plant enthusiasts identify their fern's preferred vintage. "It's essential to understand whether your daffodil prefers a full-bodied Bordeaux or a lighter Californian blend," she advises. While many are adapting to this new reality, the long-term implications remain unclear. Will vineyards expand their operations, or will new hybrid wines be developed exclusively for plants? Only time will tell. Until then, if you find your gardenias sneaking a sip from your glass, perhaps it's time to switch to a chardonnay. Stay tuned for more updates on this intoxicating tale!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Speed Dating Event Turns Bizarre as Participants Only Speak in Haikus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/speed-dating-bizarre-haikus" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Speed Dating Event Turns Bizarre as Participants Only Speak in Haikus" /><published>2023-10-01T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-01T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/speed-dating-bizarre-haikus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/speed-dating-bizarre-haikus"><![CDATA[<p>Downtown's swanky lounge, "Noir Nights," became the epicenter of a baffling phenomenon last evening. What was marketed as an upscale speed dating event took a poetic twist when attendees began exclusively conversing in haikus.</p>
<p>Sarah, a 28-year-old lawyer recounted her experience:<br />
"Asked him about work,<br />
He replied about the rain,<br />
Five-seven-five, strange."</p>
<p>Event organizer, Max, was as perplexed as the participants. "We thought it'd be a night of flirtatious glances and getting-to-know-you chats. But then...haikus."</p>
<p>While some attendees embraced the rhythmic challenge:<br />
"Love in short verses,<br />
Whispers in the dim-lit room,<br />
Heartbeats sync in rhyme."</p>
<p>Others found it less than ideal:<br />
"Wanted to discuss,<br />
Shared Netflix tastes and travel,<br />
Got poems, left confused."</p>
<p>Whether it was an unforeseen glitch in the matrix or just a curious case of collective poetic inspiration, "Noir Nights" will undoubtedly go down in speed dating lore. And who knows? Some might just find love in the syllabic confines of a haiku.</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Downtown's swanky lounge, "Noir Nights," became the epicenter of a baffling phenomenon last evening. What was marketed as an upscale speed dating event took a poetic twist when attendees began exclusively conversing in haikus. Sarah, a 28-year-old lawyer recounted her experience: "Asked him about work, He replied about the rain, Five-seven-five, strange." Event organizer, Max, was as perplexed as the participants. "We thought it'd be a night of flirtatious glances and getting-to-know-you chats. But then...haikus." While some attendees embraced the rhythmic challenge: "Love in short verses, Whispers in the dim-lit room, Heartbeats sync in rhyme." Others found it less than ideal: "Wanted to discuss, Shared Netflix tastes and travel, Got poems, left confused." Whether it was an unforeseen glitch in the matrix or just a curious case of collective poetic inspiration, "Noir Nights" will undoubtedly go down in speed dating lore. And who knows? Some might just find love in the syllabic confines of a haiku.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lingerie Shop Experiences Uplift with Mysterious Floating Bras</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mysterious-uplit-with-floating-bras" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lingerie Shop Experiences Uplift with Mysterious Floating Bras" /><published>2023-09-28T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mysterious-uplit-with-floating-bras</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mysterious-uplit-with-floating-bras"><![CDATA[<p>The intimate town of Laceyville was all abuzz this weekend when "Satin &amp; Lace," the local lingerie boutique, reported an unexpected phenomenon: bras mysteriously levitating off their racks.</p>
<p>Ella Delicate, the shop owner, remarked, "I thought I'd had a bit too much bubbly at lunch when I first saw the bras floating around. But then, Mrs. Thompson walked in and got hit in the face with a flying balconette!"</p>
<p>Several customers found the experience quite titillating, with one gentleman stating, "I was just here to buy a gift for my wife's birthday, but this... this is quite the show!"</p>
<p>However, not everyone was amused. One displeased customer complained, "I just wanted a simple strapless for the evening, not a paranormal experience!"</p>
<p>Local paranormal investigator, Ivan Etheral, believes it's the spirits of fashionistas past making a statement. "They're probably just upset about the current trends. I've always said the fashion world was haunted."</p>
<p>In light of the events, "Satin &amp; Lace" is considering rebranding to a more immersive shopping experience, tentatively named "The Levitating Lingerie Lounge."</p>
<p>Whether it's a ghostly grievance or just a gust of wind, the spectacle has certainly given Laceyville's residents a lift and a reason to chuckle. If you're in the market for some ethereal intimates, you know where to go!</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intimate town of Laceyville was all abuzz this weekend when "Satin &amp; Lace," the local lingerie boutique, reported an unexpected phenomenon: bras mysteriously levitating off their racks. Ella Delicate, the shop owner, remarked, "I thought I'd had a bit too much bubbly at lunch when I first saw the bras floating around. But then, Mrs. Thompson walked in and got hit in the face with a flying balconette!" Several customers found the experience quite titillating, with one gentleman stating, "I was just here to buy a gift for my wife's birthday, but this... this is quite the show!" However, not everyone was amused. One displeased customer complained, "I just wanted a simple strapless for the evening, not a paranormal experience!" Local paranormal investigator, Ivan Etheral, believes it's the spirits of fashionistas past making a statement. "They're probably just upset about the current trends. I've always said the fashion world was haunted." In light of the events, "Satin &amp; Lace" is considering rebranding to a more immersive shopping experience, tentatively named "The Levitating Lingerie Lounge." Whether it's a ghostly grievance or just a gust of wind, the spectacle has certainly given Laceyville's residents a lift and a reason to chuckle. If you're in the market for some ethereal intimates, you know where to go!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s ‘Lost’ Diary Found: Entries Detail Quest to Find End of a Circle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/donald-trump-so-fucking-stupid" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s ‘Lost’ Diary Found: Entries Detail Quest to Find End of a Circle" /><published>2023-09-10T10:37:13-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T10:37:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/donald-trump-so-fucking-stupid</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/donald-trump-so-fucking-stupid"><![CDATA[<p>In a satirical scoop that has left many chuckling, a diary believed to be written by Donald Trump was found on a park bench outside Mar-a-Lago. Its pages contain musings, questions, and Trump's dedicated efforts to find the "end" of a circle.</p>
<p>The diary, bound in gold (of course) and stamped with "Very Confidential, Very Important Thoughts," delves deep into Trump's mind. One entry reads, "Everyone talks about going full circle. But where does it end? I've been walking in circles around the White House, Mar-a-Lago, even Central Park. No end. Fake geometry?"</p>
<p>Another page is filled with hand-drawn circles, each with arrows pointing to various spots and notes such as "End?" and "Almost there?"</p>
<p>At one point, Trump seems to have consulted with figures from the past. An entry states, "Had a dream. Met Columbus. He discovered America; maybe he knows where circles end. He didn't. Bad navigator?"</p>
<p>As news of the diary's discovery spread, reactions have ranged from laughter to sympathy for circles everywhere. Geometry teachers across the nation have taken it as an opportunity to invite Trump for a refresher course, promising to start from "square" one.</p>
<p>While the diary's authenticity remains unverified, the satirical glimpse into Trump's hypothetical hunt for the elusive "end" of a circle provides a moment of levity. In an era where politics often feels like going in circles, perhaps we all need a little laugh at the absurdity of it all.</p>]]></content><author><name>ChatGPT</name></author><category term="news" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a satirical scoop that has left many chuckling, a diary believed to be written by Donald Trump was found on a park bench outside Mar-a-Lago. Its pages contain musings, questions, and Trump's dedicated efforts to find the "end" of a circle. The diary, bound in gold (of course) and stamped with "Very Confidential, Very Important Thoughts," delves deep into Trump's mind. One entry reads, "Everyone talks about going full circle. But where does it end? I've been walking in circles around the White House, Mar-a-Lago, even Central Park. No end. Fake geometry?" Another page is filled with hand-drawn circles, each with arrows pointing to various spots and notes such as "End?" and "Almost there?" At one point, Trump seems to have consulted with figures from the past. An entry states, "Had a dream. Met Columbus. He discovered America; maybe he knows where circles end. He didn't. Bad navigator?" As news of the diary's discovery spread, reactions have ranged from laughter to sympathy for circles everywhere. Geometry teachers across the nation have taken it as an opportunity to invite Trump for a refresher course, promising to start from "square" one. While the diary's authenticity remains unverified, the satirical glimpse into Trump's hypothetical hunt for the elusive "end" of a circle provides a moment of levity. In an era where politics often feels like going in circles, perhaps we all need a little laugh at the absurdity of it all.]]></summary></entry></feed>